Guide to the Kitchen Sink Papers (finding aid title): Has all of the things, or at least most of them, 2000-2020ish RL.99999
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kitchen Sink Papers: Has all of the things (or most of them)
Bulk, 1989-1999
Date expression (AT outputs this instead of date range as EAD, uses date range if this empty)|||
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.99999
1.0 Cubic feet Container summary|||
Abstract without a label content -- 1st note input, 2nd note on "Notes etc" tab: |||
3rd note input: abstract content|||
Dimensions note no label |||
Dimensions note with label text of content|||
General physical description note no label |||
784 Linear Feet
5.1 Gigabytes Audiovisual objects in RL00090-SET-0001 are not included because they require Audiovisual processing before access!!
Material specific details note no label |||
Physical facet note no label |||
Box Container 1 indicator (is this container tag?) |||
Folder 1-collection-level-instance-do-we-even-do-this?
Separated Materials label |||
Separated Materials note content 1st note in "Notes, etc" tab, umpteenth note added, but dragged to first note position in notes tab in AT. It appears that the note order in AT has some impact on the note order in the resulting EAD. It looks as if those notes that go outside the DID are exporting simply in the order in which they appear in AT. |||
Kate's -- note -- about -- input |||
All generic text I added is meant to indicate the type of input field in the AT. Text I added has three pipes at the end of it ||| unless it was impossible due to the type of data (numeric). Data from related tables (e.g. Repository name) does not have three pipes, nor does text generated from the style sheet. I did not use pipes in text from real-world examples.
Accruals note
Accruals content without label -- 2nd note input, 3rd note on "Notes, etc." tab: |||
Accruals note label|||
Accruals note content. 4th note input. |||
Appraisal note
Appraisal note without a label content |||
Appraisal note label|||
Apprasal note content. 6th note input. |||
Arrangement note label |||
Arrangement note content |||
Arrangement note
Arrangement note content. 7th note input, then dragged and dropped. No label. |||
Biographical/Historical note
Biographical historical note without label content. Note inserted placement by clicking in list of notes. |||
Biographical historical note label |||
Biographical historical note content |||
BiogHist with Chronlist label |||
Chronlogy Title |||
1991 ||| 1991 event 1 ||| 1991 event 2 ||| 1991 wrapped in title tag event 3 |||
1992 1992 event |||
1993 1993 event |||
Conditions Governing Access note
Conditions governing access note content no label |||
Conditions governing access note label (accessrestrict) |||
Conditions governing access note content (accessrestrict). 8th note input. |||
Custodial History note
Custodial history note content no label |||
Custodial history label |||
Custodial history content |||
Existence and Location of Copies note
Existnce and location of copies note no label |||
Existence and Location of Originals note
Existence and location of originals note no label |||
File Plan note
File plan note no label |||
File Plan Note label |||
File Plan note content |||
General note
General note content no label |||
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Acquisition information note content no label content wrapped in corpname tag |||
Acquisition information note label |||
Acquisition information note content |||
Legal Status note
Legal status note no label |||
Legal status note no label |||
General note label |||
General note content |||
Other Finding Aids note
Other finding aids note content no label |||
Other finding aids note label |||
Other finding aids note content (otherfindaid) |||
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Physical Characteristics and Technical requirements note content |||
Related archival materials note label |||
Related archival materials note content |||
Related Archival Materials note
Related archival materials note content no label |||
Scope and Contents note
This note has some EAD formatting tags!: Emph Bold!, Emph Italic, Emph Bolditalic!, Title Bold!, Title Italic!, Title Underline!, Title Doublequote. Here's some other stuff that's not formatted.
Here's some inline tagging that should be displayed but not indexed:
The persname, corpname, subject, geogname, famname, date, and genreform, should all display exactly the same on the line below:
The persname, corpname, subject, geogname, famname, date, and genreform.
Scope and contents label |||
Scope and contents note content |||
Separated Materials note
Separated materials note content no label |||
General Note in ASpace
Text of a note entered as "General" in ASpace (is this odd or note?)
Scopecontent note label (note contains a table)
This note contains a table, taken directly from: https://www.loc.gov/ead/tglib/elements/table.html
John Albemarle (1760-1806) Mary Frances Delaney (1769-1835) John Delaney Albemarle (1787-1848)
Does anything above display?
Bibliography
Bibliography note no "title" content ||| 5th note input. Can be wrapped in tags thus (but why not bibref?):
content in blockquote|||
Bibliography note "Title" area (in other notes this box is labeled "label") |||
Simple note in bibliography.
Bibliography Item 1
Bibliography Item 2
Bibliography Item 3
Index title|||
Index note with four entries |||
Item value in index 1 ||| Reference text 1 |||
Item value in index 2 ||| Reference text 2 |||
Item value in index Series 3 folder 1 ||| Reference Text in index to series 3 folder 1 |||
Aged women--United States; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Veterans -- Pensions
- Series title of series with Series-level notes with labels |||, 1880-1900; Series I |||; 2.0 Cubic feet; Series-level abstract text|||; Series-level dimensions text |||; Series-level general physical description text |||; Series-level material specific details text|||; Series-level physical facet text|||
  Series-level accruals label|||
  Series-level accruals text|||
  Series-level appraisal label|||
  Series-level appraisal text|||
  Series-level arrangement label|||
  Series-level arrangement text|||
  Series-level biographical/historical label|||
  Series-level biographical/historical text|||
  Series-level conditions governing access label|||
  Series-level conditions governing access text|||
  Series-level custodial history label |||
  Series-level custodial history text |||
  Series-level existence of copies label |||
  Series-level existence of copies text |||
  Series-level existence of originals label |||
  Series-level existence of originals text ||
  Series-level file plan label |||
  Series-level file plan text |||
  Series-level general note label |||
  Series-level general note text |||
  Series-level immediate source of acquisition label |||
  Series-level immediate source of acquisition text |||
  Series-level legal status label|||
  Series-level legal status text|||
  Series-level other finding aid label|||
  Series-level other finding aid text|||
  Series-level physical characteristics and technical requirements label|||
  Series-level physical characteristics and technical requirements text|||
  Series-level related materials label|||
  Series-level related materials text|||
  Series-level scope content label|||
  Series-level scope content text|||
  Series-level separated materials label|||
  Series-level separated materials text|||
  Series-level bibliogrpahy title
  Series-level bibliogrphy note|||
- Series title of Series with Series-level notes without labels|||, Series II |||; 3.0 Linear feet; abstract, series-level text, no label |||; dimensions, series-level text, no label |||; general physical description, series-level text, no label |||; material specific details, series-level text, no label |||; physical facet, series-level text, no label |||
  Accruals note
  accruals, series-level text, no label |||
  Appraisal note
  appraisal, series-level text, no label |||
  Arrangement note
  arrangement, series-level text, no label |||
  Biographical/Historical note
  biographical historical note, series-level text, no label |||
  Conditions Governing Access note
  conditions governing access, series-level text, no label |||
  Custodial History note
  custodial history, series-level text, no label |||
  Existence and Location of Copies note
  existence of copies, series-level text, no label |||
  Existence and Location of Originals note
  existence of originals, series-level text, no label |||
  File Plan note
  file plan, series-level text, no label |||
  General note
  general note, series-level text, no label |||
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  immediate source of acquisition, series-level text, no label |||
  legal status, series-level text, no label |||
  Other Finding Aids note
  other finding aid, series-level text, no label |||
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
  physical characteristics and technical requirements, series-level text, no label |||
  Related Archival Materials note
  related materials, series-level text, no label |||
  Scope and Contents note
  scope content, series-level text, no label |||
  Separated Materials note
  separated materials, series-level text, no label |||
  Bibliography
  bibliography, series-level text, no label |||
  - Item title of item with Item-level notes, labled and unlabeled |||, ca. 1880-1900; Abstract note content at folder level, no label |||; Abstract note content at folder level|||; Dimensions note content at folder level, no label |||; Dimensions note content at folder level |||; General physical description note content at folder level, no label |||; General physical description note content at folder level ||| (Box 1, Folder 1, Image 123456789987654321-alphanumeric-long-ass-child-container-indicator)
    Accruals note content at folder level, no label |||
    Accruals note label at folder level |||
    Accruals note content at folder level |||
    Appraisal note content at folder level, no label |||
    Appraisal note label at folder level |||
    Appraisal note content at folder level |||
    Arrangement note content at folder level |||
    Arrangement note label at folder level |||
    Biographical/historical note content at folder level, no label |||
    Biographical/historical note label at folder level |||
    Biographical/historical note content at folder level |||
    Conditions governing accessl note content at folder level, no label |||
    Conditions governing access label at folder level |||
    Conditions governing access note content at folder level |||
    Custodial history note content at folder level, no label |||
    Custodial history note label at folder level |||
    Custodial history note content at folder level |||
    Copies note content at folder level, no label |||
    Copies note label at folder level |||
    Copies note content at folder level |||
    ORiginals note content at folder level, no label |||
    Originals note label at folder level |||
    ORiginals note content at folder level |||
    File plan note content at folder level, no label |||
    File plan note label at folder level |||
    General note content at folder level, no label |||
    General note label at folder level
    General note content at folder level |||
    Multi-part general note label |||
    Ordered List title
    Ordered list item 1
    Ordered list item 2
    Ordered list item 3
    Ordered list item 4
    Ordered list item 5
    Scope and Contents
    This note has some EAD formatting tags!: Emph Bold!, Emph Italic Emph Bolditalic! Title Bold! Title Italic! Title Underline! Title Doublequote Here's some other stuff that's not formatted.
    Here's some inline tagging that should be displayed but not indexed:
    The persname, corpname, subject, geogname, famname, date, and genreform, should all display exactly the same on the line below:
    The persname, corpname, subject, geogname, famname, date ,and genreform.
    Bibliography note at folder level, no title |||
    Bibliography title at folder level
    Bibliography note content at folder level |||
    Bibliography item at folder level
- Series title of Series with Generic instances, box-folder type numbering|||, Series III |||
  - Folder title of Folder 1|||
  - Folder title of Folder 2|||, 1880-1900 (Box-folder 1.2)
  - Folder title of Folder 3 |||, ca. 1880 (Box-folder 1.3)
  - Folder title of Folder 4||| (Box-folder 1.4)
  - Folder title of Folder 5 ||| (Box-folder 1.5)
  - Folder title of Folder 6 ||| (Box-folder 1.6)
  - Folder title of Folder 7 (folder with a container summary) |||, no date; 2 folders (Box-folder 1.7)
  - Folder title of Folder 8 (folder with a footage) |||, [1890?]; 2.0 Linear feet (Box-folder 1.8)
  - Example with an electronic record (master) DAO, 4 folders (Box 4)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Electronic records consist of 303 image files (JPEG format) extracted from USB thumb drive, approximately 0.07 gigabytes.
  - Example with an electronic record (use copy) DAO
  - Duke University Web Directory, 2011-ongoing
- Series title of series with Generic instances, boxes and folders in separate fields in instances This text is wrapped in title tag|||, ca. 1880-1900|||; Series IV |||; 1.0 Cubic feet
  - Folder title of Folder 1 |||, ca. 1880-1900; UniqueID1|||; 0.1 Linear feet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Folder title of Folder 2 (Singular and Plural Extent Tests)|||, 1880-1900; UniqueID2|||; 1 audiocassettes 2 audiocassettes 1 audiovisual items 2 audiovisual items 1 boxes 2 boxes 1 cdrs 2 cdrs 1 CD-Rs 2 CD-Rs 1 copies 2 copies 1 files 2 files 1 film feet 2 film feet 1 folders 2 folders 1 gigabytes 2 gigabytes 1 items 2 items 1 leaves 2 leaves 1 linear feet 2 linear feet 1 megabytes 2 megabytes 1 minutes 2 minutes 1 photographs 2 photographs 1 reels 2 reels 1 tapes 2 tapes 1 terabytes 2 terabytes 1 volumes 2 volumes 1 disks 2 disks 1 DVD 2 DVD 1 DVDs 2 DVDs 1 slides 2 slides 1 prints 2 prints 1 albums 2 albums 1 VHS 2 VHS 1 VHS tapes 2 VHS tapes 1 sheets 2 sheets 1 pages 2 pages 1 discs 2 discs (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Folder title of Folder 3 |||, ca. 1880; UniqueID3||| (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Folder title of Folder 4 |||, 1880; UniqueID4||| (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Folder title of Folder 5 |||, 1880; UniqueID5||| (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Folder title of Folder 6 |||, 1880; UniqueID6||| (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Folder title of Folder 7 (folder with a container summary) |||, 1890; UniqueID7|||; 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Folder title of Folder 8 (folder with a footage) |||, 1890; UniqueID8|||; 2.0 Linear feet (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Series title of series with Generic folders, no instances, unique identifiers instead |||, 1880-1890; Series V |||
  - Folder title of Folder 1 |||, UniqueID3.1|||
  - Folder title of Folder 2 |||, UniqueID3.2|||
  - Folder title of Folder 3 |||, UniqueID3.3|||
  - Folder title of Folder 4 |||, UniqueID3.4|||
  - Folder title of Folder 5 |||, UniqueID3.5|||
  - Folder title of Folder 6 |||, UniqueID3.6|||
  - Folder title of Folder 7 |||, UniqueID3.7|||
  - Folder title of Folder 8 |||, UniqueID3.8|||
  - Folder title of Folder 9 |||, UniqueID3.9|||
  - Folder title of Folder 10 |||, UniqueID3.10|||
  - Folder title of Folder 11 |||, UniqueID3.11|||
  - Folder title of Folder 12 |||, UniqueID3.12|||
  - Folder title of Folder 13 |||, UniqueID3.13|||
  - Folder title of Folder 14 |||, UniqueID3.14|||
  - Folder title of Folder 15 |||, UniqueID3.15|||
- Series title of series of Real folder/item examples |||, Series VI |||
  Series-level access restriction on c01
  - Subsubseries title of Rawls papers lots of notes in folder-level descriptions |||
    - Philosophy 168, Kant lectures, Part I, The Content and of the Moral Law, lectures 4-9, 1977 Spring; Legacy ID: 1900-23 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Kant supplement notes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Kant supplement notes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      80-year restriction applies.
    - Striker lectures, Following Nature, A Study of Stoic Ethics. Wallace Lectures, Oxford, 1984, revised 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Modern Moral Philosophy, Philosophy 171, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Philosophy 171, Hume, 1979, Fall 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Explanatory notes transcribed from folder front flap:
      Of the Original Contract
      Justice as An Artificial Virtue and Definition of Property
      Judicious Spectator and Principle of Utility
      Kate's -- note -- about -- input
      Notes from folder flap are in an ordered list with a title (i.e. head>) filled in. Don't understand why these are numbered in the AT style sheets, they ought to simply be bulleted.
    - Hume notes, Justice and Artificial Virtues, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries title of subseries of Harvard University archives examples using Box and Folder type instances|||
    - Subsubseries title of graphic materials in folders |||, HUV 2181
      - Watercolor drawing of Christ Church, ca. 1781, 1 drawing (Folder 1)
      - Watercolor drawing of a group of four houses on Holmes Place, ca. 1781; 1 drawing (Folder 2)
        Cambridge (Massachusetts)--Buildings, structures, etc.; Houses; Watercolors (paintings)
      - A Plot of Cambridge Common with a view of the Roads & a principal part of the Buildings thereon, ca. 1781; 1 drawing; 18 x 25.5 in. (Folder 3)
      - A Plan of the Colleges with the Land Adjoining containing about six acres as survey'd in June 1784, 1 drawing; 10.25 x 19.5 in. (Folder 4)
  - Subseries title of subseries of Schlesinger examples |||
    Subseries-level access restriction on c02
    A second accessrestrict on the c02!
    - Donor lists removed from #95.12., 118F+B.14
      WRITTEN PERMISSION REQUIRED UNTIL JANUARY 1, 2041.
      A second accessrestrict on the c03!
      In this example, I put nothing into the label area for access restrictions note and folder number is in the component unique identifier field.
    - Donor lists removed from #95.12. (Folder 118F+B.14)
      Access restrictions
      In this example, I labeled the conditions governing access note. Folder number is in an instance.
    - Complete level II training packet, 1982; [disassembled] (Folder 14.20-14.21)
      includes printed material, meeting notes, and evaluations.
    - Mass Choice annual plan, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 15.11)
      See also #109F+B.1 for timeline.
      Content
      includes reports, memoranda, timelines, and budgets.
      Scope and content note with label. Instance is Box-Folder type.
  - Subseries title of a subseries of Baker examples |||
    - Subsubseries title for folders with component unique identifier as folder-box numbers |||
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption, Research, 1933; Box 2, f. 1
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption, 1933; Box 2, f. 2-3
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption [Typescript], 1933; Box 2, f. 2-3
    - Subsubseries title of folders with instances of Box-folder type |||
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption, Research, 1933 (Box-folder 2.1)
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption, 1933 (Box-folder 2.2-3)
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption [Typescript], 1933 (Box-folder 2.2-3)
    - Subsubseries title for folders with instances of Box and Folder type |||
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption, Research, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
      - Report, An Estimate of Future Copper Consumption [Typescript], 1933 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
- ELIZABETH BLODGETT AND LIVINGSTON HALL, 1823-2006; Series I
  Storage Units Summary
  File units:
  1.1 through 28.2
  Memorabilia:
  85.1m
  Oversized folders
  Box 87, Folders 1-4
  Box F+87, Folders 1-4
  Folio drawer
  1
  Audio tapes
  T-354 reels 1 and 2